♪♪♪
♪ Turn down the lights ♪
♪ Turn down the bed ♪
♪ Turn down these voices ♪
♪ Inside my head ♪
♪ Lay down with me ♪
♪ Tell me no lies ♪
♪ Just hold me close ♪
♪ Don't patronize ♪
♪ Don't patronize me ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't make you
love me if you don't ♪
♪ You can't make
your heart feel ♪
♪ Something it won't ♪
♪ Here in the dark ♪
♪ In these final hours ♪
♪ I will lay down my heart ♪
♪ And I'll feel the power ♪
♪ But you won't ♪
♪ No, you won't ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't
make you love me ♪
♪ If you don't ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I'll close my eyes ♪
♪ Then I won't see ♪
♪ The love you don't feel ♪
♪ When you're holding me ♪
♪ Morning will come ♪
♪ And I'll do what's right ♪
♪ Just give me till then ♪
♪ To give up this fight ♪
♪ And I will give
up this fight ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't make you
love me if you don't ♪
♪ You can't make
your heart feel ♪
♪ Something it won't ♪
♪ Here in the dark ♪
♪ In these final hours ♪
♪ I will lay down my heart ♪
♪ And I'll feel the power ♪
♪ But you won't ♪
♪ No, you won't ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't
make you love me ♪
♪ If you don't ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ain't no use in you
trying to make me, baby ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪♪♪